Torelli, Sue Collection of CIRL Annual Meeting Materials 6363
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sue Torelli Collection of CIRL Annual Meeting Materials
1965-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Torelli, Sue
Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL)
6363
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Reportts, pamphlets, correspondence, publications.
8300042
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 31, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5171: Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL). Records, 1978-1996. 5171 P: Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL) 38th Annual Conference Photographs 6359: Melba Kibildis CIRL Annual Meeting Materials 6359 P: Maria Cataflio CIRL Photographs
Torelli, Sue; Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL)
8300042
- 32nd Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 33rd Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 35th Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 38th Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 40th Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 41st Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 42nd Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 43rd Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 44th Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 45th Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 46th Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 47th Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 48th Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 49th Annual Meeting Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 49th Annual Meeting Plannning, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 49th Annual Meeting 3.5" floppies, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  3 computer disks
- 49th Annual Meeting Attendee Responses, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 49th Annual Meeting Welcome Packets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 49th Annual Meeting Conference Packets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 49th Annual Meeting Handouts, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Tape 1, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  May 4, 1995.
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Thomas L. Mains, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  May 5, 1995.
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Walter Licht, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Janice Bellice, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: John Paul MacDuffie, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Peter Cappelli, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 49th Annual Meeting Transcripts: Business Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  May 6, 1995.
- 49th Annual Meeting Notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 49th Annual Meeting Photographs, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  5 color photographs
- 50th Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 51st Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 52nd Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- 53rd Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- 54th Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- 55th Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- 56th Annual Meeting, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- 57th Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- CUIRL Chronology: 1946-1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Committee of University Industrial Relations Librarians. Prepared by Hazel C. Benjamin
- Cooperative Exchange Project, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Pair University Research Groups and Libraries, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Library Acquisitions Lists, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Exchange Bibliographies, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- CIRL Newsletter, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Unnumbered, May 1985
- Industrial Relations Directors, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Electronic Mail Conference Instructions, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- The Labor Unions, Dun & Bradstreet, and Dialog: The Attempt to Restrict Access, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  News clippings
- 1st CIRL Automation Survey, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- CIR News, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  University of Toronto, Centre for Industrial Relations. no.1 (1995:Jan.) and no.2 (1995:Apr.)
- CIRL Chronology of Meetings, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Compiled by Nancy Barkey Young
- Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 50)